 Mikael Seriman : **Lets begin**
 Mikael Seriman : Status of the Klingon Task Force
 Tactical: Sir, All three ships have weapons locked on us. The main vessel is armed to the teeth.
 Mikael Seriman : Hail them
 Johnathan McBride : Looks like they wanna pick a fight with the finest ship in....what's left of the fleet.
 Operations: General Kro'tek on screen now, Sir.
 Matthew Rosalini : I hear we are rebuilding the fleet shouldn't be too long. but i am ready to fly circles around them.
 Mikael Seriman  stands and straightens his jacket
 Mikael Seriman : General..I think we both know what's going on down at that facility.
 Mikael Seriman : There is only one reason why Kron'os would send one of their most advanced battle cruisers this far out on short notice...
 Galia Iadyl sits back and sips her coffee, looking totally relaxed and confident.
 Kro'tek: HOW DARE YOU!
 Mikael Seriman : No sir...How dare you!
 Mikael Seriman : What's going on down there is a war crime. It is beneath anyone who would dare call themselves a warrior race!
 Kro'tek: You would presume to lecture us! When we received the prisoners from your own Section 31?
 Mikael Seriman : Well, thank you for confirming what until now was only suspicion.
 Johnathan McBride  chuckles softly and listens quetly
 Kro'tek: And what are you going to do about it? You and your escorts are far away from home...and there's no one who can help you. Your fleet is in tatters.
 Mikael Seriman : Well, it's true that my task force is pretty far from the nearest fleet base or battle group...that being said..we can definitely outrun your ships..and I'm willing to bet that we can hold up in a firefight long enough to go to warp. Then, it's just a matter of taking this to the Federation Council. I wonder if Chancellor Martok knows about this?
 Kro'tek: You've just signed your own death warrant...
 Mikael Seriman : **THE LEAD KLINGON SHIP OPENS FIRE**
 Mikael Seriman : Helm, evasive maneuvers, Tactical return fire!
 Sh'Lira Shran "Weapons control, let's see if we can knock out their warp nacelles!"
 Matthew Rosalini : Aye Sir! evasive manuevers, setting course 141 mark 5, I could try and get under them sir, give a clear shot to their nacelles
 Johnathan McBride : whew! lets dance!
 Mikael Seriman : Shey, scan for the changeling ship. Tell them that we will give them cover and they can use this time to get down there and try to find their compatriots
 Mikael Seriman : Galia...try to get some sort of Comms to the Klingon High council
 Galia Iadyl finishes her coffee and picks up her PADD... "Aye aye Admiral...."
 Sh'Lira Shran nods "Aye admiral... Science let's see if we can find their ship"
 Mikael Seriman : McBride..try raising the Berkley and the Helmsley...order them to try and flank the Klingons
 Matthew Rosalini : Sir, i can get a bit closer to give more cover but i wouldn't suggest more than 3000 kilometers.  any closer and our shield might not hold against Klingon Disruptors, new ship refit or not.
 Mikael Seriman : do it
 Mikael Seriman : Damage Report on the Klingon ships
 Matthew Rosalini : yes sir  moving to 3000 kilometers, 1/4 impulse speed.
 Galia Iadyl: "Admiral, I've connected with General Martok's chief Adjutant, they say they can TRY to have the General online in a few minutes. "
 Mikael Seriman : Well let's hope we're still here
 Matthew Rosalini : that few minutes could end up with us and every other ship nothing but space dust sir. just pointing that out
 Mikael Seriman : They've stopped firing
 Johnathan McBride : They're going wide to flank Sir.
 Mikael Seriman : Plot an intercept.
 Mikael Seriman : angle our shields
 Mikael Seriman : Lock all weapons on the lead ship. Let our escorts work on their flankers
 Matthew Rosalini : aye sir, plotting an intercept. should have interception vector in a few seconds.... got it.  moving to intercept at 170 mark 95, full impulse, weapons i can only give you a few seconds if the admiral orders to fire, any closer than i get to them now and we could be toast.  those disruptors are stonger than i have seen before
 Johnathan McBride  nods "Formation orders have been relayed. Divide and Conquer.
 Mikael Seriman : fire all weapons!
 Mikael Seriman : Damage Report!
 Galia Iadyl sends a comm to medical, ordering them to send someone to the bridge, just in case...
 Galia Iadyl sits up.. "Admiral, I have General Martok on comms."
 Mikael Seriman : On screen
 Galia Iadyl whispers: "On Screen Sir.."
 Mikael Seriman : Chancellor Martok. This is Acting Chief of Starfleet Operations Admiral Mikael Seriman aboard the USS Imperium.
 Martok: Admiral...my aide says that you're in a rather dire predicament. In combat with a Klingon wolf pack?!
 Mikael Seriman : That's correct Chancellor. In orbit over a...classified facility on Pheben IV.
 Martok: I know of no such facility. What is going on there?
 Mikael Seriman : Apparently, Section 31 transferred some...changelings that it had been experimenting on over to some of your scientists, who continued their work. It is the same type of changelings as those who assisted in the recent Borg attack
 Martok: Are you certain of this, Seriman?
 Mikael Seriman : Positive sir. That's why the Changelings have been trying to destabilize this region. It was a ruse to get Klingon forces away from the area in order to affect a rescue. When we confronted them, they told us what they were trying to do. That's when the Klingon Force under General Kro'tek appeared and attacked.
 Galia Iadyl sends an encrypted file with evidence backing up the situation to Martok
 Galia Iadyl: 
 Martok: Kro'tek? That Had'ibah! He is an honorless cur! I will have words with him...withdraw to a safe area, Seriman while I order him to stand down
 Mikael Seriman : Understood..Imperium Out.
 Sh'Lira Shran taps on her console "Damage reports are in, sir... shields are down to forty-two percent. We have minor damage to the hull along the starboard nacelle and one blown shuttle-bay door was destroyed."
 Galia Iadyl: "Now, lets just hope that Kro'tek listens to his boss.... "
 Mikael Seriman : with Klingons though...the house usually supercedes the Chancellor when it comes to loyalty.
 Johnathan McBride : The Klingon hasn't really had a great track record of that.
 Sh'Lira Shran looks puzzled a moment then her eyes widen and she calls out "Sir, I've just received word from the changelings! It seems that they were successful in liberating their own from the facility here"
 Mikael Seriman : **THE KLINGON FLEET HAS STOOD DOWN AND SET COURSE OUT OF THE SYSTEM**
 Mikael Seriman  sighs in relief...stand down from Red Alert
 Johnathan McBride  sighs softly and wipes his brow.
 Johnathan McBride : Diplomacy isn't an easy thing.
 Sh'Lira Shran wrinkles her nose
 William Bruce shouts: Chief Bruce: All Hands secure from General Quarters
 Johnathan McBride : So what's to be done about the facility on the planet? That's not exactly something we can ignore, recent past events in mind.
 Mikael Seriman : Not much we can do. It's an internal matter of the Empire.
 Sh'Lira Shran's terminal lights up "Sir, I have an incoming signal from Admiral Janeway"
 Mikael Seriman  raises an eyebrow..."on screen"
 Sh'Lira Shran nods "on screen"
 Mikael Seriman : Admiral Janeway..I was about to contact you.
 Janeway: Admiral Seriman, I just had the most interesting communication with Chancellor Martok and President Chekov.
 Mikael Seriman : I'm sure you did, sir.
 Janeway: Wanna tell me what the hell has gone on out there?
 Mikael Seriman  looks around to his crew.."Well, we did our best to try and clean up a big damn mess of our own making, sir."
 Janeway: Oh? How so?
 Mikael Seriman : The destabilization that has been going on in this region hasn't been a Cardassian or Klingon issue...well, not at the root. The Rogue Changelings...the ones that Section 31 experimented and tortured...were behind it. They were trying to draw the Klingon Navy away from a classified facility on Pheben IV. There was a lab there where Klingon...scientists...were conducting similar experiments on changelings that S31 had given them"
 Janeway: I see. And these Klingons had some muscle backing them..and these were the ones who attacked you and your escorts?
 Mikael Seriman : Correct. We had matters in hand, but fortunately, we were able to contact the Chancellor who was able to order General Kro'tek to stand down and prevent any bloodshed.
 Janeway: Understood. Any significant damage to your ships?
 Mikael Seriman : Minor damage to the Imperium. Still waiting for Damage reports from the Berkley and the Helmsley.
 Janeway: Understood. I'm ordering the Berkesley and the Helmsely to Starbase 271 for any repairs and servicing. You're to report back to Earth, Admiral. You and your staff are supposed to be helping me run things here in the interim...remember?
 Mikael Seriman : Yes sir. We'll be home directly.
 Janeway: We'll see you when you arrive. Janeway out.
 Sh'Lira Shran frowns "I feel like we're being run around in circles"
 Mikael Seriman : John...get me damage reports from the other two ships. I want to know what's going on with them before we cut them loose.
 Galia Iadyl smiles  "Sometimes it's very handy keeping track of back-channels.  Chancellor Martok's adjutant, a Klingon named K'tharr Warrav... he and several of his fellow Klingons  and I have done some drinking together, awhile back. "
 Mikael Seriman : drinking buddies are handy buddies.
 Johnathan McBride : Aye Sir, I'll have those right away.
 Mikael Seriman : and what's going on, Number One, is damage control on a geopolitical scale
 Mikael Seriman : We need allies to have our backs right now
 Mikael Seriman : so we're not going to accuse the Klingons of anything
 Mikael Seriman : and they're not going to bring up Section 31
 Mikael Seriman : we're all going to look like good guys while we look the other way and sweep things under the rug
 Galia Iadyl: "Well, Section 31 doesn't really exist.. "
 Galia Iadyl coughs behind her PADD..
 Mikael Seriman : mhm...and that antique black starfleet insignia I have in my quarters doesn't mean a thing, I suppose
 Johnathan McBride  reads through the reports "Both ships have had minor damage to the hull and the Helmsley is patching up their impulse engines. All in all, it could have been worse." he continues reading "Shall I send them on their way?"
 Mikael Seriman : Go ahead Captain with my thanks.
 Johnathan McBride : Aye Sir.
 Sh'Lira Shran smirks "Well, it's like you said, sir... it IS an antique, so write it off as a sin of the past?"
 Mikael Seriman : If only sins of the past, stayed in the past, Number One...
 Mikael Seriman : Mr. Rosalini..set a course for Earth, Slipstream speed.
 Matthew Rosalini : Aye sir. course set.
 Mikael Seriman : gun it
 Sh'Lira Shran: "Perhaps we should banish those sins to the future"
 Mikael Seriman : Perhaps we should...
 Johnathan McBride  chuckles
 Johnathan McBride : We HAVE done a little time travel before. Perhaps a little more can't hurt.
 Mikael Seriman : Have you ever walked in on yourself before John? Very disconcerting...I'd prefer not to do that again...
 Sh'Lira Shran: "tsk tsk tsk... Sins to hide other sins is never a good idea"
 Galia Iadyl: "I really hate to say it, but some sins really are necessary.  If nothing else, than to keep us from getting so rule-entangled that we can't get anything done. "
 Johnathan McBride : Can't say I have sir. that's something I imagine I wouldn't want to do.
 Mikael Seriman : Especially when they're young and not grey..no wrinkles..very depressing...*chuckle*
 Mikael Seriman : Some sins, yes...hence I have a "wide lattitude" stance when it comes to the Prime Directive.
 Mikael Seriman : However...what Section 31 does..that's too much.
 Galia Iadyl: "I won't subscribe to generalizations like that, Sir, but I will say that this most recent ... issue, the experiments and all that, that was both unsanctioned, and very wrong."
 Johnathan McBride : even secret shadow organizations need oversight
 Galia Iadyl: "True, true.  Though part of the problem with most oversight is maintaining secrecy.   I've seen more than a couple organizations collapse because of a lack of info-security. "
 Mikael Seriman : I don't know of any reason for S31 that can't be handled by the covert arm of Starfleet Intelligence
 Galia Iadyl: "I wouldn't argue with that either, but then, I do have a bias. "
 Galia Iadyl smiles
 Mikael Seriman : *chuckle*
 Sh'Lira Shran smirks "I think you may have just found out the meaning of my phrase about banishing sins to the future... Secret, out of bounds groups are a very effective way to keep something generally secret, although not forever. Eventually a secret will be revealed, it's just a matter of how long that takes"
 Matthew Rosalini : Sir we are coming up on earth dropping out of slipstream in 3, 2, 1....
 Matthew Rosalini : we are out and have gone to thrusters only
 Mikael Seriman : Set a course for Spacedock
 Galia Iadyl: The opposite is true too though... with NO kind of oversight or external controls,  a group can easily become dictatorial, like the Obsidian Order.  Even the Kardassian government feared them.
 Matthew Rosalini : aye sir. setting course for space dock maxium impulse
 Sh'Lira Shran shrugs "well, that's their own fault for allowing that to happen"
 Galia Iadyl nods...
 Matthew Rosalini : sir we have docked
 Mikael Seriman : roger that.
 Mikael Seriman : Captain McBride, contact the Dockmaster and have them assign Yard Engineers for damage control
 Matthew Rosalini : alll moorings attached waiting for final command from Admiral Janeway adn spacedock command
 Johnathan McBride : Aye Sir
 Mikael Seriman : Commodore Shran, Vice Admiral Iadyl, Captain McBride, you may return to your interim duties at HQ for now.
 Mikael Seriman : Mr. Rosalini, you will reacquaint yourself with the Imperium after her refit.
 Matthew Rosalini : Sir, we are cleared to send the crew off ship, dockmaster has cleared Imperium to stand at station keeping
 Sh'Lira Shran looks up and nods "aye, admiral" then looks back at her console and taps on it, logging out
 Mikael Seriman : understood.
 Galia Iadyl: Aye Sir... and I owe one Klingon a drink.
 Matthew Rosalini : aye sir.  orders following that?
 Mikael Seriman : stand down until further orders arrive
 Matthew Rosalini : aye sir
 Johnathan McBride : We have two crews of engineers ready to board and begin repairs and a fleet of bee drones ready to work on exterior repairs Sir.
 Matthew Rosalini : *sets helm controls to standby and station keeping and gets up, facing the admiral.
 Mikael Seriman : sounds good
